in linkedin.com/in/debbiedeak

Debbie Deak

Marketing | Graphic Designer

Personal Statment

I am an experienced graphic designer and marketing professional who is passionate about delivering quality campaigns, projects & events.

I am quick to create ideas, concepts and develop creative solutions to problems. I am able to work on my own initiative and demonstrate the high level of motivation required to meet the tightest of deadlines. I am motivated to further my skills. and take regular courses to advance my knowledge.

Skills

Computer skills

Knowledge in Adobe Creative Suite including InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Premiere Pro. Microsoft Office packages including Word, Excel, and Powerpoint. HTML & CSS, Wordpress, Mailchimp, Google Analytics

Design Skills

Create design assets for video, adverts, and imagery, to be implimented on the website, social media, campaigns, events & other projects.

Communication skills

Friendly manner, confidence, ability to deal with people, situations, and problem solve.

Marketing Skills

Social Media Marketing, Update Website CMS, Event Management

Education

2021- Present

Postgraduate Diploma in Digital Marketing Digital Marketing Institute

Professional Diploma in Digital Marketing Digital Marketing Institute

2009 - 2011

HND Visual Communications University of The Highlands And Islands, Perth UK

2003 - 2007

BA Fine Arts - Illustration Montclair State University, NJ, USA

40 hour Prenatal and Postnatal Yoga Intensive Samadhi Family Yoga, Perth Yoga Studio, Perth, UK

200 Hour Yoga Teacher Certification Yogaflow Body And Mind, Oakridge, NJ, USA

Hobbies

I have been a yoga instructor for the past 12 years, and am passionate about yoga and pilates and fitness. I have been an avid horserider for the past 25 years. Also I love the creative arts, and travel.

Experience

Parental Leave

September 2020- Present

Marketing Campaign Manager (contract)

Origo, Edinburgh, UK August 2019-August 2020

Organised Origo's events, social media planning, updating website with new PR posts, events and services. Created design assets for Origo including video, adverts, and imagery, to be implimented on the website, social media, campaigns, events & other projects.

I am passionate about marketing and design with focus on deliverying quality campaigns, projects and events. My main goal was to further Origo's reach as a consistant and strong brand in the financial service industry.

Design Executive (contract)

Nettl of Glasgow, Glasgow, UK May 2019 - August 2019

Exceptional customer service, design & computer skills, extremely adaptable to new situations and learns new skills quickly.

Skilled in communicating with clients over the phone, via email, and in person. Projects include business branding, brochures, programmes, and exhibition stands.

Freelance Graphic Designer

Stirling, UK

May 2018 - August 2019

Projects include: branding, leaflets, product design, stationary, print production, website

Graphic Designer/Artworker (contract)

Harvey Nash, Edinburgh, UK

18 March 2019 - 18 April 2019 (5 week contract) Heriot-Watt University, Edinburgh, UK

18 October 2018 - 30 November 2018 (6 week contract) Heriot-Watt University, Edinburgh, UK

Design for print and digital media, install signage and visuals for Open Day Events & Winter Graduation for Media Services at Heriot Watt University. Adhering to brand guidelines for the University while also creating eye catching designs.

Design Executive

Printing.com/Nettl of Edinburgh, Edinburgh, UK Jan 2016 - May 2018

Pre-Press Operator/Designer

Tradeprint, Dundee, UK Nov 2013 - Jan 2016

Freelance Graphic Designer

Auchterarder UK July 2013 - Nov 2013

Graphic Designer/Digital Print Operative (contract)

Minuteman Press, Dunfermline UK Nov 2011 - Aug 2012

Graphic Designer (work placement)

Printing.com, Dundee UK Sept 2011 - Nov 2011

Student Intern

Scottish Institute for Enterprise & Centre for Enterprise,

University of the Highlands and Islands, Perth, UK

Aug 2010 - May 2011

Promote entrepreneurship to students, the community. Including small businesses and social

Marketing, event planning, including competitions, & design for events.

My role required excellent communication, leadership, time management, analytical thinking, and marketing strategy skills.